Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world is a riot of color
Truth and lies are clouding our eyes
Use your heart and truly see
You'll find the truth is not far away
Hey you could do better, truth and lies
You can't escape the gray smoke of the heart
Bring along all of your courage
Maybe then you can save this wish
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy Mojo Spy
In the previous story, the evil organization, the Illumin-Eye, gathered many treasures:
Angel's Tear, Ugly Dog's Blood, Ocean Princess,
Lamenting Voice, Heart of Vitality,
Kolitas Flower and Eternal Flame.
They planned, according to the Illumin Doctrine's instructions,
to use these treasures to open the Gate of Civilization.
The only clue left for Locky and the others was a photo left behind by Tolrus.
Can they stop the Illumin-Eye's scheme?
The Ark Ceremony
After a long night of waiting,
enduring countless hardships,
we have finally arrived.
This dawn of hope
I am honored to announce
All the offerings needed to open the Gate of Civilization
have been collected in full
My faithful followers
Your tireless labor
has moved even the heavens themselves
Blessed be his grace
The greatest day in history
has finally arrived
To open the Gate of Civilization
that brings love and ideals to the world
we spared no blood or sacrifice
This merit shall be sung by generations to come
A world free of deceit
free of rampant materialism
where all are equal
where all despise filthy desires
a pure new world
will be forged by our own hands
And we are the saviors
the gods rising from this mire
Our great cause of love and ideals
will awe the entire world
It will be etched into the annals of history forever
Passed down through generations in people's hearts.
Good.
Then let's begin preparing the sacred ritual.
During the fierce battle in the golden monkey incident,
we accidentally got the photo Dorothy dropped—
a group photo from inside The Illumin-Eye.
The photo shows
that The Illumin-Eye's true lair
is hidden in some supermarket in Tuna Town.
The Illumin-Eye has already stolen seven items of divine power.
I bet they're following The Illumin Doctrine
and getting ready for the final evil ritual.
We're running out of time.
We have to find their hidden supermarket lair as soon as possible
and stop their last scheme.
That's true,
but there must be hundreds of supermarkets here.
How are we supposed to find it?
The best way is to search them one by one.
Let's start with the Tuna Supermarket next door.
This time, we'll catch those fiends and bring them to justice.
Captain, I'll gather the team.
Hello! Please support us, The Illumin-Eye!
The Illumin-Eye will transform the world into a pure, beautiful place.
Hello! Please support The Illumin-Eye!
The Illumin-Eye will bring you love and dreams!
Thanks!
Hello!
Please support our Illumin-Eye!
Then hold more sales!
Hello!
Please support our Illumin-Eye!
Hey there, kid!
Be a big supporter of the Illumin-Eye, okay?
It's you!
What are you doing here?!
Don't tell me your hideout is this supermarket right next to the police station?!
The most dangerous place is often the safest.
You didn't see that coming, did you?
You snake in the grass!
Last time you played us for fools!
Now you're trying to escape?!
Darn it!
Officer, is that all you've got?
No more tricks!
Oh no!
Go! Surround him!
Look! Miss MU and her rumored boyfriend are shopping at the supermarket!
Here they come!
Dorothy, are you ready?
Rest assured, Lord Eye.
The Illumin-Eye! Surrender to us now!
Today is the end of you rotten villains!
Help!
The Great Light Ark—
is born!
The moment has finally come!
Actually, sometimes
the end of the world doesn’t feel too bad.
Now I’ve fully unleashed the energy of all seven sacrifices!
Brilliant, Lord Eye!
Mm. Use these divine sacrifices
to wipe out those ugly parasites!
Fail this time, and don’t come back.
Yes, Lord Eye.
There’s nothing quite like
one soul, lonely and alone.
Life, after all,
is bound to hold some sorrow.
Saying goodbye to today
always leaves us feeling lost.
Look at tomorrow
Waving to me at the horizon
Every day is just sunrise and sunset
Turning through time, dreaming of more
Hoping that in life
every second, every moment
bright eyes will keep shining
with a smile that meets the sun
Bravely speak the little feeling treasured deep inside your heart
A morning breeze blows in
and carries away the wishes of all these years
It will quietly arrive at the crossing of Thousand Shores Station